No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Osman Bey!
Sir, Nicola retreated after Togay.
We have to retreat immediately.
I'll take revenge for my brother someday!
Kalanoz!
Osman Bey, Kalanoz escaped.
Your brother is after him.
You should go, too.
Brother.
Kalanoz!
So it's you before Osman, Savcı Bey.
Osman killed my brother.
Now I'll kill...
Brother!
You are wounded.
This infidel's dagger
won't kill me brother.
Go after him.
I'll see you in the tent.
Hold on. Hold on.
Come on my brother.
Go.
Sir.
Togay baited my army to Osman...
by retreating.
It seems he's not done yet.
Where is Kalanoz.
He wounded Savcı Bey heavily.
I saw Osman was going after him, sir.
Osman won't stop when he smells blood.
He'll find Kalanoz.
Togay!
Damn your gods!
All your gods shall damn you!
You are the only reason I am losing!
It's you!
Why are you falling back our soldiers
who tasted blood, Commander Togay?
You were Balgay's son.
You were Geyhatu's bloody wolf.
What are you now?
I'm the brother of Osman Bey who fights
for Allah and his tradition.
Why did Osman Bey send you?
Osman Bey wants to become a state
in Ilhanlı...
under Geyhatu's domination.
Osman Bey obeyed Black Shaman Togay.
Osman is now our state.
He'll pay taxes to us.
Your victory has become a graveyard
to your family, Osman.
Now it'll be your grave.
I swear that I'll bury you alive!
I'll bury you alive!
I took revenge for my brother.
I ripped your brother's lungs!
Nicola will...
rip your bowel.
Brother, brother.
Our victories shall go on brother.
Brother, you need to recover first.
We will go on. Just heal up.
We'll grow...
with many victories.
Easy.
Brother.
- Brother.
Why didn't you kill Kalanoz?
Why?
Killing him is a gift to him, brother.
Come on, we're going to the tent.
Where is the sledge? Alps1
- Osman.
- Brother.
Listen to me.
Listen to me brother.
Listen to me Osman.
I had a dream last night.
Brother!
My father...
was waiting for me...
under the tree...
- He planted when he came back to Sögüt.
- Brother
Brother!
My son Bayhoca was also there.
The tree's glorious body connected...
its roots on the ground...
to its branches in the sky.
My father...
said we became martyred...
- For our state.
- Brother!
People die...
Brother.
State...
is eternal...
State is eternal.
I fought on your side,
on my brother's side...
on our valiant alps' side...
on my son's side...
I fought
Shahada...
is waiting for me.
No.
My son Ertugrul...
and my Hatun Lena...
- are entrusted to you.
- Brother.
They are entrusted to you.
Take a good care of them.
State is...
eternal.
Brother, brother.
State is...
eternal.
"I bear witness that none
deserves worship except Allah, ...
Brother!
and I bear witness that...
Muhammad is the messenger of Allah."
Brother.
Bury this dog's body...
in that hole.
From now on, we are not going to stop
Yes my Bey.
As you command my Bey.
My valiant brother.
My martyr brother.
My brother who...
made Ikızce Hill our land with
his own blood.
Brother.
Go, with Allah's name.
While you go to the other side...
to the banner of our prophet...
your murderer's body is in that hole,
Brother.
Don't worry.
How can she do that? How can my daughter
and alps join the war without notifying me?
My daughter joins Osman and goes
to battlefield and you are unaware, right?
Answer me!
My Bey, forgive my Bey.
She didn't tell anyone.
She'll pay for this when she comes back.
We are trying to get along with Nicola....
but my daughter fights against him!
We would be vanished if you
guys had the command!
Allah forbid, she may get...
Allah forbid my Bey!
Malhun Hatun's sword is sharp!
- She is as good as you in battlefield.
- She is, she is.
My Lord forbid.
But when she comes back safe and sound...
she'll pay for this.
She is like his father.
She does what she believes in.
But she has to learn to obey
Bey's command.
You can go.
Don't fall into carelessness again.
Forgive me my Bey.
It won't happen again.
My Lord, you discpiline us with troubles.
You only take to give better.
You took Bayhoca from me, you
gave me Islam.
My son is now in heaven.
My Savcı is on war. May you make them
victorious my Lord.
I was honoured with Islam.
May you grant all the people with Islam.
Amin..
Thank you my Lord.
My Savcı is back. Thank you.
Osman Bey, may Allah bless our martyrs.
But where is my man Savcı Bey?
Father of my Ertugrul...
where is he?
Ertugrul Ghazi's son...
Savcı Bey...
Keep me sane my Allah.
Savcı!
Savcı, get up.
You told me you'd come back.
Get up.
You promised me.
Our Ertugrul is crying.
He understands he is losing you.
Savcı, open your eyes.
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey how can I bear this pain?
Savcı is gone.
My Bey, my Bey...
He is gone.
Savcı open your eyes please.
Aygül, Savcı is a martyr now.
My Savcı is a martyr.
Lots of us has become martry, Lena.
Lots of us.
I am a mother of a martry.
I am a wife of a martyr.
This is good, right Osman Bey?
I shouldn't cry, should I?
I must draw myself up, mustn't I?
Lena Hautn...
I cannot tell you not to cry...
but you should be fortitude.
You are a Muslim after all.
Alps!
Kayı's valiant Hatuns!
Valiant alps!
My Beys!
By respecting this mother of
a martyr...
wife of a martyr...
and all of our martyrs...
we are not going to celebrate our victory.
Our breed is always remember my
brother valiant Savcı Bey...
even a thousand years from now.
This is what I want from Allah.
My brother valiant Savcı Bey wanted to
get down from his horse...
and become a martyr...
to hug his son.
He laid down with his
beautiful face and...
saluted our Prophet.
He fought against the devil infidels!
Now what we must do...
is to say farewell our martyrs and
my brother.
We defeated the enemy.
We won.
Take my brother to my tent
for his last journey.
Get all the martyrs ready.
Lena...
-May I enter, my bey?
-Thank Allah.
Come in.
Doesn't your ears hear your father?
How can you go to jihad without
telling me?
Forgive me, my bey. But it was an important
battle. We couldn't stay aside.
Did we make a mistake by standing aside?
Did we commit a sin?
Of course not, my bey.
But you missed a great good deed.
-You would be glad to be there.
-What happened there?
What did we miss?
We slaughtered the heathens.
But Savcı Bey...
is fallen.
-Savcı Bey!
He is a martyr?
Oh, Savcı Bey, oh...
Osman Bey is hurt badly then.
The heathen Kalanos killed him, father.
Osman Bey took his revenge.
But revenge doesn't bring back
what's gone.
Firstly, his nephew. Now, his brother.
Bahadır!
Yes, my bey.
Malhun Hatun and I will go to
Kayı Tribe.
We need to go to Savcı Bey's
funeral.
Lord Nikola will think that our agreement
is broken.
We are the ones who betrayed the deal
for the second time.
He might attack our tribe.
Have measures.
-As you order, my bey.
-Get ready.
Lena, be glad that your son and husband
are in heaven now.
Come on, ladies. Let's give the
beys some space.
Come on. Come on, Lena.
Come on.
My scholar brother.
My wise brother.
I'm a witness to that...
even when he was competing
against me...
he did it for the tribe,
not for himself.
After I became a bey,
he stood with me...
with his blood and bones.
Neither after the fall of his son...
nor after I refused his wishes,
did he show any discontency.
You have my blessing.
May Allah bless you as well.
Kayı Beys are ghazis while
holding their swords...
and martyrs when they die.
Lions who carry the future of the Turks
on their shoulders...
have this fate. Savcı...
Savcı was a Kayı bey.
He lived with honor and he died
for Allah.
-We are all witnesses.
-We are.
To his faith, to his personality...
his virtues.
He lived as a Muslim,
he died as a Muslim.
May Allah accept him to heaven.
Oh, my great-hearted brother.
Even we didn't know the charities you
did.
Now, those oppressed and poor people
are orphans without you, Savcı.
But don't worry. Their prayers
are always with you.
May you rest in heaven.
Your son is united with your husband
in heaven, my daughter.
You are a Muslim who is
honored with Islam...
and forgiven for her past sins.
You will join them one day.
Thank Allah that Allah is gathering
you in his heaven.
This earth is short-lasting, my daughter.
The other life is what's important.
Those who win the other life can't lose.
Let's farewell the honorable son of Kayı,
ghazi and martyr Savcı Bey.
With the name of Allah.
Come on.
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar! La ilahe İllallah!
He gives you fire from the wet tree...
and you set fire with it.
As Allah who created the earth and
the sky created them...
can't he resurrect people too?
Of course, he can! Because he can
create again and again.
He knows everything.
When he wants to create something,
he only says ''Exist!''...
And the thing starts existing
at once.
Allah has a reign over everything...
that lays on earth.
Don't forget that you all will be
summoned before him...
to be questioned.
Reads Qur-an
My beys, you all came here to
share our pain.
-May Allah bless you all.
-Amin.
My sheik, you just said ''He only lacked
a coat''.
-What does that mean?
-Kumral Abdal.
Two beys were paying for the food
that our lodge is giving to people.
One of them is still alive.
Let's not speak his name.
The other was Savcı Bey, my sheik.
He didn't want it to be known.
He had a lot of money.
That's why he was paying.
Is that so, Akça Dervish?
My sheik, he had no store nor any
land nor a wealth of a bey.
He gave everything left from his
wife and children.
My good brother.
He had a horse, armor, and weapons.
Nothing else.
That's what a dervish can have.
Here is a weapon...
drawn for Islam.
Now, this is the legacy
of a great Kayı bey...
to the Kayıs.
This weapon will be given to his
son Ertuğrul.
He will continue the cause of
world order.
With all the other alps who are born
in Kayı Tribe...
he will go to war.
With this weapon.
This cause won't be forgetten.
One of us dies and thousand of us
are born.
Let's leave the Kayı beys alone.
With the name of Allah.
We won a great victory, Osman Bey.
A great victory.
Savcı Bey died seeing and knowing this.
This is my only consolation, Bamsı Bey.
But, this Togay...
why did he retreat from the battlefield,
Osman Bey?
Osman Bey, you seem to know why.
If you want to divide the enemy,
there is a way, Osman Bey.
You will discard one of them from
your enemy list.
You can convince Togay.
Togay? But...
Togay is a heathen Mongol.
The only way to make peace with
the Mongol is to bow down.
Or, making it look like
bowing down.
Bowing down...
becoming a vassal.
However you call it.
That tyrant will believe it.
We won a great victory
with this game, but...
But if tyrant Togay was involved,
we don't know what would happen.
It's one of the first lessons my ghazi
father taught me about war.
Don't fight two enemies at once.
We'll destroy both heathens
separately, Osman Bey.
Don't doubt that. No enemy of Kayıs
has died a natural death.
-Thank Allah.
-It won't change.
Now, listen to me well, beys.
After our mourning ends,
we'll lit the fire of jihad again.
-Inshallah.
-Now, get rest.
With Allah's approval, Osman Bey.
Inshallah.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you.
Thank you.
One day later
May I enter, Lena Hatun?
Come, Bala Hatun.
We came to farewell you.
-May Allah bless you.
May Allah bless you too, Lena.
I will miss your black and
sad eyes.
I was such a trouble for you.
You have my blessing, Lena Hatun.
Give me yours.
What are you saying?
It's yours.
Don't forget us.
Come visit us.
Gonca.
You came elegantly and you
are leaving elegantly.
You left a noble mark in
this tribe, Lena.
-Gonca.
-Thank you.
Hearing this from such a noble
woman like you is honoring.
Thank you.
Forgive me for drawing my sword
against you.
It was my crazy times.
Is it different now?
Our children...
Our children will grow up fatherless.
We share the same fate now, Lena.
Aygül...
-Give me your blessing.
-It's yours.
It's yours.
Kulucahisar isn't far away.
Come visit me.
Don't live us lonely.
Of course, we will.
We won't leave you or my nephew.
I can't stay in this tent anymore.
That's why I leave.
I will miss you, ladies.
I will miss you.
Give me your blessings.
May Allah protect you.
You too.
It's like I was stabbed
in the heart.
I bore many of the mischiefs
of the heathens.
But the heaviest of the betrayal...
the blow that came from the closest
was the heaviest.
Bala. What did you do?
Tell me.
Did you do what I told you?
Food was handed out for
three days, my bey.
The poor was given a hand.
They prayed for Savcı Bey
and you.
Thank you, Bala.
What about Lena?
She went to Kulucahisar safely
with the alps.
Your nephew Ertuğrul is
safe with her.
Mashallah, Bala. Mashallah.
-May Allah bless you.
-You too, Osman.
May I enter, Osman Bey.
Come.
Beys, this is the end of our mourning.
But our pain will always stay
in our heart.
The enemy won't stay idle.
We need to talk about our measures.
Togay still thinks that
you will pay taxes.
Let him come. We set our game.
We broke their alliance
with the heathen Nikola.
Nikola won't stay idle.
He'll do anything to take revenge for
Malhun Hatun's aid.
We can increase the defenses, Osman Bey.
We can send soldiers to Umur Bey.
We won a great victory, but...
it costed heavly.
Let's not give any more casualty.
To protect Umur Bey, we need
a guarantee.
What kind of a guarantee is that?
Togay.
I will go to Togay.
If he wants us to stay a vassal...
then, he'll stop Nikola
from attacking Umur Bey.
What will we do about Süleyman?
No news from Melik. He must be dead.
Melik was going to bring information
from Nikola.
He failed to do that.
They failed to save their lives.
Now...
Süleyman will pay for it.
Isn't that so, Bamsı Bey?
Osman Bey, he will pay heavily.
Don't you worry.
Lord of Bilecik
sent his regard, Lord Nikola.
Lord of Nikea sent 100 of his cavalry,
Lord Nikola.
Lord of Bursa said that he is with
İnegöl.
Do you know why you come here?
Either victory or death!
There is no other option.
Now, get rest.
With the newcomers,
we have 300 soldiers, Nikola.
300 soldiers. Just in three days,
we have a big army.
Everything is ready to strike the Turks.
We are very close now, Nikola.
I can't wait to attack Umur's tribe...
and storm at him.
Osman's mourning will be
our feast.
I wait for his mourning to end.
I will go and ask Osman Bey.
What does it mean to be the
vassal of the Mongol?
What kind of a valiancy is paying
taxes to Togay?
Don't you know Osman Bey, my bey?
Would he be a vassal to the Mongol?
-Haven't you heard it with your ears?
-It's clearly a plan, father.
-Let's not go there like this. Then--
-Then, what, Malhun?
-Then, we'll be embarrassed.
-Is that what you think?
-Do you know what I think?
-Tell me, my bey.
-I'm listening.
-I think that you deserve a punishment.
As you order, my bey.
You have the right to punish me.
It's better for you to go to Engürü,
to your uncle.
To Engürü? What will I do there, my bey?
I should be here.
I should be with you.
Give me whatever punishment you
want in here, father.
Let me be with you,
support you.
It's better if you don't be
with me for a while.
You'll understand it better that you are
opposing me instead of helping me.
This is your punishment.
When I receive the news I'm waiting
for, you'll move.
You can't do this! Osman Bey promised me!
You can't do this!
Osman Bey is a man of his word.
He said that he'll forgive you for
you to bring news.
But you have failed.
Right, Bamsı Bey?
What does that mean?
Simon died. The mission that my
bey has given is left unfinished.
Let me go!
You will go.
You will go, Petros.
But firstly...
you will pay for Süleyman and Melik that
you killed and stole their names...
and for my hand.
-Then, you'll go.
-How will I pay?
-With this.
-Petros.
You will talk to my injured hand.
Without putting blood on my hand,
let me go, Bamsı Bey.
My blood is halal for you, Petros.
But firstly, pay the price...
then, Cerkutay will take you to
our borders.
Don't you worry.
This is for that child that we named
after Süleyman Shah!
And this is for many of our Alps
that you killed.
Now, you've paid the price.
Son.
When you came to Bamsı Bey's tent,
I didn't like either of you.
I was right.
Say hi to Simon.
Stop.
-What's happening?
-They want revenge for their warriors.
They should think about
their own lives.
Stop!
-My bey.
-Göktuğ.
Stay here.
Now, you are here.
You finally bowed down to Ilkhaganetei
to khan of khans, Geyhatu.
Or, have you come here...
to ask for something in return?
We made a deal.
If one of us changes his mind...
everything will be ruined.
-Don't you forget that.
-A deal is a deal.
You are a vassal.
-Tax date is coming.
-Its time will come.
Because Malhun Hatun fought
aside me...
Nikola will want to get revenge.
Do you want me to stop him?
Umur Bey and all the tribes in
these lands...
are under my protection.
If they get attacked...
I'll take it personally.
Gökbörü gets its strenght from
its faith, not from its pack.
Its faith becomes the faith
of its pack.
If you don't break that faith,
it will break you.
It will do it without putting its
fangs on you.
Gökbörü who protects its pack...
came here to show its fangs
to me, Togay the Dark Shaman.
How will I trust your word?
Your messenger will bring you
the gold...
and you will see that.
We'll see, Osman.
We'll see.
Be at ease.
If the tribes are under your protection.
Nikola is in my palm.
We'll see.
What did you tell the Mongol, my bey?
He knows what I told him.
But what he doesn't know is...
what I didn't tell him.
-What will you do, Togay?
-After carrying our Geyhatu's orders...
I will rip out Osman's heart
and eat it.
I remember the things we lost
because of my father. How could he?
How could he?
How can one betray his own tribe.
I'm not crying because I love him,
but I'm ashamed.
Some people...
are called by their fathers' names.
Because they don't have
anything else.
They aren't a thing
on their own.
I heard that...
Osman Bey called you Aygül Alp the
Ghazi of Kulucahisar.
You are the leader of the warriors
women of the Kayı.
And for me, you aren't Dündar Bey's
daughter.
-And what am I?
-Aygül the Mad.
And so am I.
They don't know my parents.
When I was a child, they would call me
Cerkutay who was raised by weasels.
Then, Cerkutay the Bandit,
Cerkutay the Commander...
Now, I'm an alp of the Kayı.
But I was always Cerkutay.
Just like you, crazy girl...
You were always Aygül.
And you will remain so.
I never thought you could
speak so smart.
You eased my heart.
Then, I should leave before
ruining it.
Good.
And you...
Nevermind.
Don't get cold.
-Welcome, Umur Bey.
-Thank you, Osman Bey. Thank you.
But I'm not well.
What's wrong, Umur Bey.
I buried 3 sons of mine.
Three sons by the sword of the Mongols.
They killed my lineage.
What is this taxing news?
What does it mean to be a
vassal of the Mongols?
I did it to break their alliance
with Nikola.
If we were to fight with Togay
as well..
we would lose more than
my brother Savcı.
You say that it's a plan of yours.
Did I get it right, Osman Bey?
Instead of trading with Nikola, you sent
Malhun Hatun and her alps to me.
It helped us.
That's what fits you, Umur Bey.
But Nikola will seek revenge.
But Togay will stop Nikola
because of the taxes.
This plan will be a secret
between you and I.
No one will know it.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
We know how to keep a secret.
If Nikola comes, we have the
power to fight back.
He won't.
Osman Bey, I don't find it appropriate
to keep it a secret.
My daughter Malhun came to your aid
without my order.
-You didn't order it?
-No.
She acted on her own. She took the
alps and came to your aid.
Soldier!
Do you Mongols always abandon
your allies on the battlefield?
With Geyhatu's order, now I'm the
lord of the Ilkhaganete's border.
Everything of the Turk tribes; their blood
their bone, their flesh, their taxes...
the taxes of the lords,
they are all mine.
-Is that so?
-If the lords don't obey me...
I'll let the Turks join me and come to
your castle to take it from you.
Togay.
What do you want?
Osman became a vassal of Ilkhaganate.
Did Osman tell you that?
I betrayed you, Togay.
You betrayed me.
But you haven't seen the
real treachery yet.
Osman will betray you so bad that
you will come here to...
beg me for an alliance.
If Osman does such a thing...
he won't see the anger of Togay
but the wrath of Ilkhaganate.
We'll see. It won't take long.
We will see.
Not only Osman. Umur Bey too will
be under my protection.
Those who don't listen to my word will...
see such a great army upon them that...
these lands will be washed in blood.
What will we do? What will we do, Nikola?
What will we do?
We were defeated heavily at Domaniç
We lost many.
We'll be patient.
We can't face the Mongols.
Osman won't be a vassal to
the Ilkhaganete.
He is playing with them.
He is making time to get power.
He is stopping the Mongols and us.
Osman is playing with them.
Osman is playing with them!
He is playing!
The real question is: what will we do?
What will we do?
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come.
Osman Bey says that it's a plan.
Says that he did it to break the alliance
of Nikola and Togay.
He says he didn't truly join
the Mongols.
I knew it, my bey.
I knew that Osman Bey wouldn't do that.
Does he know that the heathen Nikola
will want to attack us?
He'll talk to Togay to
stop that.
He thought well. Osman Bey is a good
politician.
We don't need the protection of anyone!
If you hadn't moved on your own,
we wouldn't be talking this now!
You stepped over your father.
You endangered my deal with Nikola!
Now all over Domaniç belongs to
the Turks, father!
Isn't jihad a must for the Muslims?
We were going to infiltrate İnegöl and
take that castle!
The word ghazi would recall
our names in these lands.
You endangered this opportunity
as well!
And you gave the opportunity of patronage
to Osman.
My bey father, you are mad at me.
But don't you know that he sees himself
as the guardian of all Muslims.
-This is how he set the fate of the Kayı beys.
-Osman Bey is dreaming.
I'm interested in the truth.
I will go to Nikola and
solve this matter.
My plan will continue...
and I will prove that we don't need
Osman Bey.
I wish you wouldn't go to
that castle so frequently, father...
I'm afraid that Nikola might do
something wrong.
Enough with the objections.
Your uncle's answer is here. He awaits
you. Tomorrow, you'll go to Engürü.
Malhun Hatun's valiant alps!
Know that...
these lands that you ran away into from
the Mongols is the last shelter for Turks.
And from this shelter...
we'll strike our strongest blow against
the enemy...
together, against all their treachery!
You don't look good, Malhun Hatun.
This path leads to Kayı Tribe.
This one to Engürü.
Either path I take...
my heart will be split up.
Choose the path that will
make you smile, Malhun Hatun.
I'm with you until my last breath.
Then, we are going to Kayı Tribe.
Let's go!
How aren't you too ashamed to
come here?
Your defeat, Osman's victory...
It's all in vain, Nikola.
As long as we have the Mongol
menace upon us...
we won't have victories
or routs on these lands.
As long as we have the Mongol
menace upon us...
neither victory nor defeat
can have any meaning.
we won't have victories
or routs on these lands.
neither victory nor defeat
can have any meaning.
You, who can't even control
his daughter...
Are you giving me advice...
You, who can't even control
his daughter...
while you can't even control your own
daughter?
You, who can't even control
his daughter...
are giving me advice?
while you can't even control your own
daughter?
are giving me advice?
My daughter didn't listen to me.
She didn't listen to me.
However, she will pay for this.
My daughter didn't listen to me.
But she will pay for it. I sent her to
Engürü. You won't see her again.
However, she will pay for this.
But she will pay for it. I sent her to
Engürü. You won't see her again.
You won't see her again.
But she will pay for it. I sent her to
Engürü. You won't see her again.
Is this how you'll clean your hands
from the blood of my soldiers?
Will you pay for my dead
soldiers like this, Umur Bey?
Is this how you'll clean your hands
from the blood of my soldiers?
What do you expect me to do, Nikola?
Killing my own daughter?
What do you want me to do, Nikola?
To kill my daughter?
What do you expect me to do, Nikola?
Killing my own daughter?
With you or without you,
I will continue my trade.
With you or without you.
I will keep trading.
With you or without you,
I will continue my trade.
I will enlarge my trade.
With you or without you,
I will continue my trade.
I'll grow my herds.
I will enlarge my trade.
You will grow with me or Osman
will choke you with your hate.
I'll grow my herds.
You'll either grow with me or
Osman will choke you with my hatred.
You will grow with me or Osman
will choke you with your hate.
You'll either grow with me or
Osman will choke you with my hatred.
It's your decision, Nikola.
My decision is to...
enhance my friends.
Not to create enemies...
from them
Then...
it means that my caravan...
won't work with the Lord of İznik.
Won't you take your revenge?
I won't ever forget what is done to me.
Umur Bey will...
understand that.
- Can I come in, Osman Bey?
- Come in, Malhun Hatun.
- Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
- Thank you, Osman Bey.
I heard that you disobeyed your father...
by joining the war.
You preferred Allah's order.
What happened, Malhun Hatun?
You seem different.
My Bey is angry with me because I
went the war without telling him.
- He expelled me.
- What?
Did he punish you...
for going to war with me?
I didn't want to go
without a farewell, Osman Bey.
What are you talking about, Malhun Hatun?
Wait.
What punishment is that?
I'm not dead yet!
You go to war with me...
you fight with me, you go
along with my victory...
you kill enemies...
However, you can't be...
punished for these.
He is my father.
I can't do anything.
If you can't...
I can.
Stop thinking about exile.
- How, Osman Bey?
- You're our guest.
Umur Bey will understand his mistake.
- I have to talk to him first.
- You don't have to...
He will become angrier.
We prepared
food for your Alps, Malhun Hatun.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Malhun Hatun won't go to Engürü.
She will stay here.
I will talk to Umur Bey.
You stay here.
100 soldiers are coming from
Sivas, Commander Togay.
All of the Lords and Turkmens
will obey me.
What about Osman? What if he betrays?
If you don't care about the baby animal...
you can't know it will be
a tiger when it's grown.
It will be an end for Kayı
if Osman does such a thing.
However, Osman is smart.
He worked with Geyhatu to protect
his soldiers.
Let's see if Osman sends us money...
or head.
Malhun Hatun was about to
spoil all of my works.
I had to send her.
What did you do?
Is my daughter safe?
Don't worry, my Bey. She is with the Alps.
They will meet the other
Alps on their way.
Good.
She should learn some things
if she rules this tent.
You can't be a Bey just by fighting.
You will use your mind and
you should be patient.
- Can I come in, Umur Bey?
- Come in, Oman Bey.
Welcome.
Umur Bey...
Malhun Hatun is in my tent.
In your tent?
What is she doing there?
Don't blame her.
- I stopped her from going.
- Why did you do that?
It's not the right thing to punish her.
It's between me and my daughter.
You stay out of it.
How can you disobey my order?
She helped me.
So, it's also about me!
Do you think I will stay out of it while
she is being punished like this?
You think you can do anything you want.
Don't you see that you discredit me?
Then, you won't let your daughter go...
if you don't want to be discredited.
How do you know if Nikola
does something bad?
There's no danger for us.
We have an agreement with Nikola.
- What agreement is that again?
- A new caravan is in İnegöl.
Malhun Hatun will pay for her manners.
- You stay out of it, Osman Bey!
- Umur Bey!
Can I come in?
Yes.
My Bey, Nikola sen this.
What is written on that?
These heads are the...
consequences of what Malhun did.
They say they can start the trade now.
Nikola may do something bad to
Malhun Hatun and...
he may say it's revenge for Kalanoz.
She isn't going to Engürü.
Umur Bey has his Alps heads.
Send my regards to
Umur Bey, a proud Turk Bey.
No one can harm me
without paying for what they did.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Compassionate, the Merciful.)
Enjoy it.
You talked to my father, Osman Bey.
What happened?
I talked to Umur Bey.
I said it's dangerous.
He agreed.
Then?
You aren't going to Engürü.
I wasn't expecting him to agree.
He knew he was wrong.
Then...
you can go to your tent tomorrow.
- I owe you, Osman Bey.
- Not at all.
Come on, enjoy your meals.
Mashallah.
May Allah bless your hands, my Bala.
The rice is so delicious.
Malhun Hatun did it, Osman Bey.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
- Malhun Hatun is going to her tent.
- Thanks.
Can I come in, Osman Bey?
- Come in, brother.
- I have some important news, Osman Bey.
- Tell me, brother.
Togay has more 100 soldiers now.
100 soldiers, huh?
They are the best soldiers.
It's complicated, Osman Bey.
Togay is very powerful.
And...
today is the tax day.
He will attack us
when he doesn't get money.
It seems so.
They seem so powerful.
They will cause trouble to us.
My Bey, what if you continue your trick...
you give some money and...
get Togay off of us?
What do you think, brother?
We couldn't beat them yet.
We know what Balgay did to our tent.
Then...
we should decide
which of them is more harmful.
Money or defeat?
The ambassador you've sent
has arrived in the tent, Togay.
In these lands that Ertuğrul
Bey took from Byzantine...
Geyhatu is the only ruler.
The spirits are with me.
The power of Erlik Khan is with me.
I am still suspicious of Osman.
Do you think I am trapped by Gökbörü?
Whether he will send the golds...
or his tent will be covered by blood.
What do you want?
I am the ambassador of Commander Togay.
I will meet Osman Bey.
Alps, search him up.
Look at his head.
Come on.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
I am here to take the money.
Welcome.
We were waiting for you.
Göktuğ.
Bring the golds that Togay wants.
Okay, my Bey.
You seem ready.
We don't like being late.
Thank you.
Can I come in?
Come in, Bamsı Bey.
How is Togay?
He is better now.
Mashallah.
Here...
these are from my grandfather
Suleyman Shah's victories.
These are from...
my father Ertuğrul Ghazi's victories.
My nephew Bayhoca's blood...
is on these golds.
My brother Savcı Bey...
Abdurrahman Ghazi and all of the martyrs...
has their blood on these golds.
Now...
you want to take these golds...
right?
You can.
Here you go.
Taking money from Turks is like...
taking the lion's hunting.
Tell Togay that...
Kayı Tent never gives money.
This is what a coyote...
gets from the lion.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com